谢谢你载我回家啦
Thanks for the ride home.
我还从没骑过摩托车呢
I've never been on a motorcycle before.
你很害怕是吗  抓我抓那么紧
Were you scared? You were holding on pretty tight.
啊对  不过那不是因为我害怕啦
Yeah, but that wasn't because I was scared.
行啦  明晚电影院见
Anyway, see you tomorrow night at the movies?
好啊  当然  你想让我什么时候来接你呢
Yeah, for sure. What time do you want me to pick you up?
来接我
Pick me up?
呃  话说  你其实不用来接我的
Um, you know what? You don't have to do that.
我们只要  在商场见就行了
We can just... we'll meet at the mall.
这样你就不用绕到我家来了
That way you don't have to come here.
-商场见就行了  -可是
- We'll just meet there. - Well...
就在商场见啦
At the mall.
好吧  不过我们为什么不进去逛逛
Okay, but maybe we could just, like, go in and hang out
-坐一小会儿  -不行
- for a little while. - No.
德里克  不行  如果我们现在逛的话
Derek, no. If we hang out now,
明天该说什么好呢
what will we have to talk about tomorrow,
那么就商场见咯
at the mall?
好吧  或许我们可以
Well, maybe we could...
嘘  有什么商场再说
Shh. Save it for the mall.
好的  嗯  到时见
Okay, well, I'll see you later.
嗯好  再见
All right, bye.
-那家伙是谁  -什么
- Who's the guy? - What?!
哪个家伙
What guy?
你躲着爸妈见的那个家伙啊
The guy you're trying to hide from mom and dad.
我没有
I'm not trying
躲着任何人去见任何人
to hide anybody from anyone.
泰迪  你就别和我装了
Teddy, let's not play this game.
咱俩可都知道有那么个骑着小摩托的家伙
We all know there's a guy. We all know he has a motorcycle.
咱俩还知道我这儿还有照片
And we all know I have photos.
关我屁事
So what do I care?
当然关你事  我可是个大嘴巴
You care because I can't be trusted
对于一切奸情指望我守口如瓶可不现实
with information like this.
鄙人有个外号  大嘴盖比
Gabby Gabe they call me.
好吧  你到底想怎样  大嘴盖比
Okay, just tell me what you want, gabby.
我在学校犯了点小事
I got into a little trouble at school.
班主任要找咱爸妈谈话
And now my teacher wants to talk with my parents.
这和我有什么关系
So what does that have to do with me?
问的好 泰迪
Funny you should ask, Teddy.
我该更直接点喊您 "妈" 吗
Or should I say "mom"?
噢  不行  不行  不行  不行
Oh, no no no no.
完全可以
It can totally work.
梦露老师那把年纪  眼睛看不清楚的
Miss Monroe is old and has terrible eyesight.
不行  这太不靠谱了
No, that's crazy.
我可不给你当妈
I'm not gonna pretend to be mom.
这张照片很有趣哈
Here's an interesting photo.
这个应该叫独轮技吧
I believe they call this a wheelie.
你今天的邪恶劲儿怎么全用在我身上了
Well, isn't someone being especially evil today?
因为我昨天睡的相当爽
I got a good night's sleep.
好吧  就算我答应了
Okay, so even if I do agree,
你打算找谁来当爸
who are you gonna get to play dad?
嘿  伙计们
Hey, guys.
P.J  我需要你来去学校假装我爸
P.J., I need you to be my pretend dad at school.
没问题
Sure.
你也太容易搞定了  他说什么你都答应
That's it. You're just gonna do what he says?
从长远来看  这样做省我时间
In the long run, it just saves time.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： 没有昵称  echochohoo
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  sarina
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第十集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E10  Meet the Parents
谢谢你  亲爱的
Thank you, honey.
嘿嘿
Hey hey hey hey!
是不是忘了啥呀
Didn't you forget something?
懒得每次都来
I'm not gonna do it every time.
鲍勃  你不觉得我们得为小查莉添点
Bob, do you think we should get something for Charlie
东西玩玩吗  像秋千跷跷板啥的
to play on, like a swing set or slide?
她才不需要那种东西
She doesn't need any of that stuff.
她自己在那儿有的玩得可好呢
She's got all sorts of things to do back here.
是吗  亲爱的  瞧瞧她
Really? Honey, look at her.
亲爱的  她在发挥她的想象力呢
Honey, she's using her imagination.
这树枝在她脑子里  其实是把圣剑
In her mind, that stick, it's a sword.
一根大魔杖
It's a magic wand.
-你在那儿摆弄什么呢  小查莉  -树枝
- What you got there, Charlie? - A stick.
你其实把它想象成
Which you are pretending is a...
树枝
Stick.
P.J  我们得谈件事
P.J., there's something we need to talk about.
噢别啊  我就知道会这样
Oh no, I knew this was gonna happen.
你想分手了  不是吗
You wanna break up, right?
噢  不是不是  其实我们蛮不错的啦
Oh, no no no, I think things are going really well.
我也觉得
Me too.
只是我们已经在一起三个星期了
It's just that we've been seeing each other for three weeks
还没有正经约过一次会呢
and we haven't even gone out on our first date yet.
噢  对啊  说的没错
Oh. Yeah, you're right.
我们每次出去都带着堆朋友
We've only been out with friends.
就是嘛  第一次约会能了解一个人好多呢
Yeah, and I think you learn a lot about a person on a first date.
了解什么
Like what?
了解他叫啥名儿
Like sometimes their name.
这段恋情是否能天长地久
Or if the relationship is meant to be.
-不是吧  -没错
- Really? - Yeah.
第一次约会的美好经历是整段感情的基础
An awesome first date sets the tone for the entire relationship.
杂志封面上这么讲的
I saw it on a cover of a magazine.
封面  你没看整段文章
Just the cover? Did you read the article?
没  我不喜欢看书
No, I'm not a big reader.
我们果然是一对儿
We are so right for each other.
呃呃呃  咱们是不是得说说约会的事儿
Unh-unh-unh. How do I know until we've had our first date?
嗯嗯 好啊  第一次约会你想去哪儿呀
Okay, all right, well, where do you wanna go on our awesome first date?
什么约会  没人正式邀请过我
What date? No one's asked me out yet.
-暗示暗示  -懂了
- Hint hint. - Right.
这样  好  嗯  斯凯勒  你愿意
Right, okay. Well, Skyler, would you like to...
哎呀  我的耳环好像掉了呀
Oops, I think my earring just fell out.
-糟了  -你看见掉哪儿了吗
- Uh-oh. - Do you see it?
没有  等等
No. Wait.
慢着  噢  没错  在这儿呢
Wait. Oh, yeah, here it is.
找到了  刚才说到哪儿了
Got it. Where was I?
噢  想起来了  斯凯勒  你愿意
Oh, yeah. Skyler, would you...
-P.J  你想干什么  -老爸  我不过在
- P.J., what are you doing?! - Dad, I was...
我正在问斯凯勒一个严肃的问题
I was about to ask Skyler a very important question.
你才17岁啊
You're 17 years old.
你还在咕唧鸡快餐店打工  你想毁了你自己的人生吗
You work at kwikki chikki. You wanna ruin your life forever?
我只不过在约她出去
I was just gonna ask her out on a date.
天哪
Oh.
玩得开心
Have fun.
李大宝欢乐玩具堡垒  小查莉一定喜欢死了
Li'l tots forts o' fun... Charlie is gonna love this.
现在让我把这李大宝给拆了
Now let's rip this baby open and slap her together.
喂喂喂  慢着点  慢着点
Whoa whoa whoa. Slow down. Slow down.
在你开工之前
Before we do any ripping and slapping,
我们还是先看说明书吧
we're gonna read the directions.
鲍勃  你能不能不要总是这样
Bob, that always takes forever.
亲爱的  说明书决定了这将变成堡垒还是废木
Honey, the directions are the difference between a fort and firewood.
我们才不需要什么说明书
We don't need directions.
我们只要照着箱子上的图片搭就完全可以了
All we have to do is look at the picture on the box and make that.
只要看看图片就够了
Just look at the picture and make that.
怪不得你做饭那个水平
Well, that explains your cooking.
我回屋拿眼镜去
I'm gonna go get some reading glasses.
什么都不许乱碰
Do not touch anything
等我回来
until I get back.
才不呢
I won't.
慢走啊
Take your time.
住手  喂喂喂  给我停下  你在干什么
Stop! Whoa whoa whoa, stop stop! What are you doing?
把这两片插上  马上就好了
I'm making these two pieces fit. I almost got it.
不  不  不  别再踢它了
No no, no more kicking.
我们得看说明书
We have to read the directions.
我们不用通过说明书来知道这两片
We don't have to read the directions to know that this piece
正好能插在一起
fits into this piece pretty much.
-把东西给我  -不行  你让我来做
- Gimme this. - No, would you just let me do this.
把东西给我  你完全不知道怎么搭
Gimme this. You don't know what you're doing,
你会弄伤到人的
and somebody might get hurt.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我眼前有三个你的影子
Because I'm seeing three of you right now
我连一个影子都不想看到
and I don't even wanna see one of you,
你还是自己去搭吧
I'm gonna let you build this by yourself.
多谢了
Thank you.
彼此彼此
From all of us.
盖比  你家长还来不来了
Gabe, are your parents coming or not?
梦露老师  这是几根手指
Mrs. Monroe, how many fingers am I holding up?
-三根  -嗯  他们在路上了
- Three. - Yeah, they're on their way.
-你好  -妈妈
- Hello. - Mom!
你在这儿啊  你个小混蛋
There you are, you little scamp.
打住
Dial it down.
-我是梦露太太  -嗨
- I'm Mrs. Monroe. - Hi.
真高兴见到你
So nice to meet you.
我是艾米邓肯  护士  四个孩子的母亲
Yes, Amy Duncan, nurse, mother of four.
你怎么样
How you doing?
别说了
Way down.
这是我丈夫
There's my husband.
爸爸  抱歉伙计们我来晚了
Dad? Sorry, I'm late, chaps.
我是鲍勃
I'm Bob.
邓肯先生  我不知道你原来是英国人
Mr. Duncan, I didn't know you were british.
没错  我太太也不知道
Yeah, neither did Mrs. Duncan.
不错  我就是英国人
That's right. I'm british.
怪不得您口音那么有趣
What an interesting accent.
您是来自英国的哪儿
What part of england are you from?
鸵鸟屎屎郡
Ostrich-shi-shi-shire.
什么
Pardon.
鸵鸟屎屎郡
Ostrich-shi-shi-shire.
我该不是听成了鸵鸟郡吧
I don't believe I've heard of ostrichshire.
您少说了一个"屎"  亲爱的老师
You one "shi" short, love.
爸爸  我闯祸了  咱还是说说这件事吧
Dad, I'm in trouble. Let's focus on that.
没错  盖比表现不乖
Yes, Gabe has been misbehaving
我想我们得谈谈
and I thought we should talk about it.
好的  你放心  我们知道了
Yes, rest assured, we are aware,
我们会管教他的坏表现的
and are going to put an end to this behavior.
我会把这臭小子拖去
Yes, I will be taking the young lad out
关进牧羊馅饼蜀葵屋
to the hollyhock house where we'll Shepherd his pie.
-什么  -他们鸵鸟屎屎郡的人
- What? - It's just something they say
都这么说的啦
in ostrich-shi-shi... where he's from.
-嗨  爸爸  -嗨
- Hey, dad. - <i>Hey.
你为什么戴着假胡子
Why are you wearing a fake mustache?
那你又为什么不戴
Why aren't you wearing one?
我很喜欢我俩的谈话方式
I do enjoy our talks, son.
嗯  既然都在谈了
Hey, while we're talking,
你认为完美的第一次约会应该是怎么样的
what's your idea of a perfect first date?
第一次约会  第一次约会
First date? First date.
啊  不行
No, I'm sorry.
我必须先知道胡子是怎么回事
I really need an answer on that mustache.
好吧  我正在假扮成英国版的你
Fine. I was pretending to be a british version of you.
所以说你想问约会的事啰
So you got a question about dating.
是啊  我想为斯凯勒出个好主意
Yeah, I gotta come up with something great for Skyler,
可我没什么想法
but I don't have any ideas.
月光野餐怎么样
How about a moonlight picnic?
你们可以开车上山  俯瞰城市的灯光
You can drive up into the mountains, look out over the lights of the city.
听起来很浪漫
Sounds romantic.
-当然  -我觉得很好  谢谢  爸爸
- Yeah. - I like it. Thanks, dad.
-嗯  爸爸  -嗨
- Hey, dad. - Hey.
你为什么戴着假胡子
Why are you wearing a fake mustache?
那你又为什么不戴
Why aren't you wearing one?
小查莉  转眼间
Charlie, before you know it,
你就会有比纸盒好玩儿多的地方玩了
you're gonna have something a lot better than a box to play in.
让我钉好这最后一个钉子
Now let me just finish off this last nail
就可以
and...
其实吧  纸盒也挺好玩儿的
Then again, that box looks pretty fun.
-嗨  -嗨
- Oh, hey. - Hey.
- Hey. - Hey.
-你看起来不错  -你看起来不错
- You look good. - You look good.
我们都看起来不错
We all look good.
你们能坐下吗  我们正在玩猜名人游戏呢
Would you sit down? Trying to do the celebrity word scramble here.
朱丽叶 罗伯茨
Julia Roberts!
泰迪  问你个问题
Teddy, I gotta ask you something.
你是不是不想让我去你家
Is there a reason that you didn't want me to come to your house?
不  干嘛这么说
No, what are talking about?
瑞安 雷诺兹
Ryan Reynolds.
自己想就行了
Do it in your head.
我不知道  我有点觉得
I don't know. I kinda got the vibe that maybe
你不想让你的家人见我
you don't wanna introduce me to your family.
不  不是我不想让他们见你
No, it's not that I don't want them to meet you.
是我不想让他们见你的摩托
It's that I don't want them to meet your motorcycle
还有皮靴  还有印着骷髅的
and your biker boots and your leather jacket
皮夹克
with the skull on it.
泰迪  我不想成为那种
Teddy, I don't wanna be somebody
躲着你父母的人
you have to hide from your parents.
-扎克 埃夫隆  -求你了
- Zac Efron! - Come on!
你知道吗  我喜欢你现在的样子
You know what? I like you the way you are.
这才是关键
That's all that matters.
明天晚上来吧  我让他们见见你
So come over tomorrow night and I'll introduce you.
好
Cool.
-给你  -谢谢  妈妈
- Here you go. - Thank you, mother.
那是盖比的妈妈
That's Gabe's mother.
而且那不是他丈夫
And that's not her husband.
安啦  他们可能只是朋友
Relax, maybe they're just friends.
或者不止
Or not.
还在节食吗  妈妈
Diet, mother?
你都41岁了还单身
You're 41 years old and single.
是的  还在节食
Yeah, diet.
-安吉丽娜 朱莉  -妈妈
- Angelina Jolie! - Mom!
哈  看看哪
Ha! Look at that.
它一开始在那儿
Yeah, first it was there,
现在在这儿了
and now it's here.
那儿  这儿
There, here.
-你竟然成功了  -看来某人说错了哦
- You actually did this. - Guess somebody was wrong.
-小查莉  宝贝  谁说错了呀  -爸爸
- Charlie, honey, who was wrong? - Daddy!
好吧  爸爸很感动
Well, daddy's very impressed.
还有点吃惊
And a little shocked.
妈妈要跳起胜利之舞
And mommy is gonna do a victory dance.
我对啦  你错啦
I'm right, you're wrong
-我对  你错  我对啦  -好吧
- I'm right, you're wrong, I'm right.  - All right.
现在我们倒着说
Now we're gonna switch it up.
你错啦  我对啦
Cause you're wrong and I'm right
你错  我对  你错啦
you're wrong, I'm right, you're wrong.
-我进去啦  -拜拜  西班牙语
- going inside now. - Bye-bye. In Spanish...
偶对啦  偶对啦
Estoy correcto,</i> <i>estoy correcto.
-嗨  我是蒂姆  -我是鲍勃
- hi, I'm Tim. - I'm Bob.
我们干嘛要聊天
Why are we talking?
我忘了把这个给你妻子了
Forgot to give this to your wife.
这是什么
What is it?
拼装游乐器材的账单
It's the bill for assembling your play structure.
是你装的
You put that together?
是啊  我干的不错  是吧
Yep, turned out pretty good, huh?
相当不错啊
Couldn't possibly have turned out better.
那么  如果你准备付些小费来表达你的感激之情
Well, if you'd like to reflect your satisfaction with a tip.
-拜拜  蒂姆  -我可以收
- Bye-bye, Tim. - You know, I take...
你觉得目前为止  我们的第一次约会怎么样
How are you enjoying our first date so far?
很特别啊  是吧
Pretty special, right?
这条路确实够弯啊
This sure is a twisty road.
我觉得很好  这才有意思
Which is fine with me 'cause this is fun.
呜呼
Whoo-oo!
你不在呜呼
You aren't whooing.
因为我觉得不太舒服
That's because I don't feel very well.
可能饿了吧  从野餐篮里找出点吃的
Maybe you're just hungry. Take something out of the picnic basket.
或者  放点进去
Or put something in.
你说了算
Your choice.
救命
Help!
盖比  盖比  看好查莉
Gabe, Gabe, watch Charlie!
鲍勃  怎么了
Bob! What happened?
不知道
I don't know.
我只不过是站在这儿欣赏着秋千
I was just standing here admiring the swing set...
就是那个你自己搭起来的
You know, the one you put together all by yourself...
然后突然  嘭
And then boom!
这玩意儿就倒在了我身上
The whole thing came down on top of me.
-你没事吧  -不知道
- Are you okay? - I don't know.
我就是  有点困
I just... I feel so sleepy.
不不不  鲍勃  看着我  看着我
No no no. No, Bob, stay with me. Stay with me.
艾米  你知道的
Amy, just know that
不管我怎么样
no matter what happens to me,
我不怪你把它拼装了起来
I don't blame you for the way you put this thing together.
-我去找人帮忙  -不  不
- I'm gonna go get help. - No no!
我去找  蒂姆
Let me. Tim.
啊  你认识蒂姆  是吧
Oh, you know Tim, right?
当然了  嗨  蒂姆
Of course I do. Hi, Tim.
-最近怎么样啊  -你好  邓肯太太
- How you doing? - Hi, Mrs. Duncan.
鲍勃 邓肯  你怎么可以这样吓我
Bob Duncan, how dare you scare me like that!
活该你骗我
Well, you deserved it for lying to me.
什么  我怎么不能骗你了
What? So now I can't lie to you?
我还以为我们家很和谐呢
I thought we had a good marriage going here.
这是拆卸器材的账单
Here's the bill for taking it apart.
谢谢
Thank you.
哦对了  你能不能再把它装起来
Oh, could you put this back together again please?
当然了  那么明天你想让我来
Sure, then tomorrow you want me to come back
再拆开吗
and take it apart again?
不了
No.
拜托  蒂姆  我们没疯
Gosh, Tim, we're not crazy.
真高兴你愿意再给我一次机会
I am so glad you're giving me a second chance.
我们就假装第一次约会从来没有发生过吧
Let's just pretend our first date never happened.
什么约会
What first date?
我吐在野餐篮里的那一次
The one where I puked in the picnic basket.
不不  这就是个说法
No, it's an expression.
"吐在野餐篮里"是个说法吗
Puked in the picnic basket's an expression?
听起来可流行不起来啊
I don't think that's gonna catch on.
等一下
Excuse me.
梦露老师  你来这儿干嘛
Mrs. Monroe, what are you doing here?
邓肯先生  您的口音怎么没了
Mr. Duncan, you've seemed to have lost your accent.
它来无影去无踪
It comes and goes.
啊  这就来了  嘀嘀
Ah, there it is. Pip pip.
而且您的胡子也没了
And you've lost your mustache too.
是的  胡子兴高采烈地跑了
That's right. Me mustache went cheerio.
邓肯先生  我有个坏消息
Mr. Duncan, I have disturbing news.
是关于您妻子的
It's about your wife.
你妻子  你还有妻子
Your wife? You have a wife?
-没有  -你没有
- No. - You don't?
当然有了
Of course I do.
-你是谁  -我是他女朋友
- Who are you? - I'm his girlfriend.
大家好  这儿
Hey, guys, what's the...
而她竟然和他男朋友一起来了
And here she is with her boyfriend?
你居然对我不忠  你都结婚了
You're cheating on me? You're a married woman.
-你结婚了  -不  不不
- You're married? - No. No no no.
-你没结  -当然结了
- You're not? - Of course I am.
-呃  -盖比
- Eww! - Gabe!
-怎么了  妈妈  -我开始了解
- Yes, mother. - I'm starting to see
你为什么不想让我见你的家人了
why you didn't want me to meet your family.
盖比  梦露老师发现你的父亲
Gabe, Mrs. Monroe has found out that your father
和我出了点小问题
and I are having problems.
那么  她知不知道
And does she know
你们俩就是我不乖的原因
that you guys are the reason I misbehave?
现在知道了
I do now.
好吧  也许这痛苦能带给
Well, maybe some good can come
我们一个好结果
from all this pain.
别说了
Dial it down.
梦露老师  对不起
Mrs. Monroe, if you'll excuse us,
这个家庭需要调解
this family has some healing to do.
而我只需要与我父母和他们的同伴
Which I would like to do just with my parents
一起解决
and their dates.
坚强点  女士
Stay warm, love.
不要心灰意冷啊
Don't wanna freeze off your English muffins.
爷爷  奶奶
Grandma, grandpa!
发生什么事了
What's going on?
我是盖比的老师  我来和他父母谈谈
I'm Gabe's teacher. I came to talk to his parents.
我们就是
We're his parents.
没错  爷爷  你就是我爸爸
That's right, grandpa. You're my dad.
他认为自己还是总统呢
He thinks he's the president too.
-你是谁  -我是德瑞克
- Who are you? - Hey, I'm Derek.
-就是个普通朋友  -外面的摩托是你的吗
- Just a friend. - Is that your motorcycle?
-是的  -完了
- Yeah. - No...
-我喜欢摩托车  -我俩一对的  我和德瑞克
- I love motorcycles. - We're dating, me and Derek.
你能不能别当着我的面这样
Will you stop throwing that in my face?
-我们演完了  -很好
- We're done with that part. - Jolly good.
嗨  小查莉
Hey, Charlie.
我们都因为假扮爸妈而被禁足了
Well, we all got grounded for pretending to be mom and dad,
可是有个好消息哦
but there's some good news.
很帅嘛  邓肯先生
Looking good, Mr. Duncan.
得了吧  叫我鲍勃就行
Oh, please, call me Bob.
好吧  看来我杞人忧天了
Yeah, turns out I was worried about nothing.
我的男朋友也成了我爸的好朋友了
My new boyfriend is dad's new best friend.
我是不是应该有点担忧呢
Maybe I do have something to worry about.
我和斯凯勒也没事了
And things are cool between me and Skyler,
我跟她解释了我没和我姐姐结婚
after I explained I wasn't married to my sister.
是啊  不然就太糟了
Yeah, that would have been awful.
-正如吐在野餐篮里  -是啊
- Talk about puke in the picnic basket. - Right.
-啥  -哦  就是个说法
- <i>What?</i> - Oh, it's an expression.
好吧
Yeah.
-啊哦  -我的车啊
- Whoopsie. - My bike!
好吧  纯洁的友谊要遭受考验了
Oh, well, that should put a dent in the old friendship.
还有  当然了
And of course,
你的秋千第三次坍塌了
your swing set has now collapsed three times.
祝你好运啰  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
-你干嘛呢  -抱歉打扰了  先生
- What are you doing? - Sorry to trouble you, governor,
我是从英国来到美国的
but I'm visiting the States from the u.K.
可我的车似乎在您家门前抛锚了
And me auto seems to have broken down in front of your house.
我正玩游戏呢
I'm trying to play a videogame here.
如果这故事有丁点有趣的地方  你就直接说了好不
If there's a funny part to this story, can we please get to it.
你真是个油嘴滑舌的小家伙
Saucy little bloke, aren't you?
总之  我能不能借用您家电话打给修理厂呢
Anyway, may I use your telephone to ring up the garage?
进来吧
Get in here.
盖比  是谁
Gabe, who was at the...
天哪  真是个帅小伙
By jove, you're a handsome lad.
你也是啊  英国佬
Back at you, british dude.
啥  难道你
Wh... if you're...
啥
What?
莫非你是从鸵鸟屎屎郡来的
Are you by any chance from ostrich-shi-shi-shire?
哪儿  没听说过
Where? Never heard of it.
我是从鸵鸟屎屎屎郡来的
I'm from ostrich-shi-shi-shi-shire.
啊  我少说了一个屎
Ah, I was one "shi" short.